JOHN JOSEPH D. MOJICA

194 Brgy. 10 Corregidor Gen. Trias City, Cavite 4107 +639476268326 iamjjmojica@gmail.com



OBJECTIVE:

To take a challenging role in the field of Computer Engineering which will help me acquire new skills and widen abilities I have obtained during my stay in my university. Also, I aim to have experience in a work environment where I can share my expertise with efficiency and quality.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:

2013 - 2019 De La Salle University – Dasmariñas

Dasmariñas City, Cavite

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

2009 - 2013 Academy of Saint John La Salle Greenhills Supervised

General Trias, Cavite

WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2019 – August 2019 Intern – PLDT, Field Service Engineer

PLDT Cepza Exchange Barangay Tejeros Convention, Rosario,

Cavite

SEMINARS-EVENTS ATTENDED:

2019 "DATABASE SEMINAR FOR WEB DEVELOPMENT"

Candido Tirona Hall,

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2019 "PYTHON PROGRAMMING SEMINAR"

Candido Tirona Hall,

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2018 "MAXIMIZING THE CLOUD FOR STARTUP SUCCESS"

Ugnayang La Salle

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2018 "INTERNET OF THINGS"

Ugnayang La Salle

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2018 "SOFTWARE TESTING SEMINAR"

MPH Tent

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2017 "RESEARCH WEEK PLENARY SESSION"

Ugnayang La Salle

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2016 "ELOQUENCE- ENGLISH PROFICIENCY SEMINAR AND WORKSHOP" Singapore

Ugnayang La Salle

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

AFFILIATION:

2017 – Present Member, Institute of Computer Engineers of the Philippines ICpEP Region IV-A

PERSONAL BACKGROUND:

Born on May 10, 1997 in Cavite, Philippines. Fluent in English and Filipino. Proficient in using Microsoft programs (Word, Powerpoint and Excel), Code blocks and Multisim. Knowledgeable in HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, Java and C++. Fast learner, goal oriented, optimistic, team player, hardworking and determined.

REFERENCES:

Available upon request.